gettingmarried.co.uk 2014-12-08

# Privacy Policy Statement

### GettingMarried.co.uk Privacy Policy

Last updated: 1 December 2009.

At GettingMarried.co.uk, we recognise that privacy is important. The following Privacy Policy describes the usage of information that is collected on the site, by both you and visitors to your site. If you have any questions or queries about this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us via our website at [Contact Us](http://www.gettingmarried.co.uk/contactus.php).

##   
Information Collection & Use

**Registration**  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

You have the option to provide demographic information age and gender to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalised experience on our site. 

[Incubate](http://www.incubate.co.uk/) is the sole owner of the information collected on GettingMarried.co.uk. Incubate collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site:

**  
Creating your wedding website  
**While creating your wedding website, you will be required to enter various pieces of information, including both personal details and about your wedding day. We use this information to create your website. You have complete control over what information appears on your public wedding site, and no information will ever be released to any third party.

**Interacting with your wedding website  
**When your guests interact with your wedding website, they may enter information about themselves (i.e. the lift sharing facility, RSVPing etc). This information is stored securely in our databases and is only accessible to the couple who own the site. This information will never be released to any third party. **  
**

**Sending Invitations to Friends  
**If you choose to send an invitation to a friend, we will ask you for your friend’s email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  Incubate stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral programme.

Your friend may contact us at [Contact Us](http://www.gettingmarried.co.uk/contactus.php)  to request that we remove this information from our database.

Financial details  
When purchasing a GettingMarried.co.uk DVD, GettingMarried.co.uk uses PayPal as its gateway to process credit/debit card payments. GettingMarried.co.uk does NOT store (and does not intend to store) your credit/debit card information.

###   
Uses of Information

The site uses information that you provide to create the designs on the site, and provide starting data for the site’s features. For example, if you provide a postcode of the wedding venue, the site will use this information to automatically generate maps and travelling instructions.

All information sharing is performed with the explicit consent of the user. For example, if a guest who is driving to the reception provides information about him/herself in the lift sharing section, this information will be stored on the GettingMarried.co.uk servers. However, this information will only be released to a passenger, if the driver explicitly approves the information sharing to proceed (via a link to his email inbox). If the driver does not approve of the passenger, no information sharing will occur.

## **  
Communications from the Site**

Special Offers and Updates We will occasionally send you information on products, services, special deals and promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page. You will not receive these emails unless you have registered for them.

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.” 

**Newsletters  
**If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

**Service-related Announcements  
**We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. 

##   
Customer Service

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password.  We will also communicate with you in response to your enquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

##   
Profile 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources to create a “profile” of your preferences.  We tie your personally identifiable information to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We do not share your profile with other third parties.

###   
Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)**  
We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.  This information does not identify individual users.

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information. 

**Personally identifiable information:  
**We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties 

**Service Providers  
**We use the services of Google Inc to provide mapping and geolocational services on our site.  When you sign up for your site, we will share co-ordinates of your wedding reception and ceremony with Google, as necessary for the third party to provide that service. Google does not have access to any personally identifiable information – it purely produces a map based upon input co-ordinates.

##   
Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site

## Choice/Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us via [Contact Us](http://www.gettingmarried.co.uk/contactus.php).

###   
Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyse trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We do link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

##   
Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies.  We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by GettingMarried.co.uk only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

##   
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

If you came to our site via a Google advertising campaign, we employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us which advertisements are effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

To learn more about Google’s use of clear gifs, please go to [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.” 

## **Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Incubate. Please be aware that we, Incubate, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

## **  
Bulletin Boards/Chat Rooms**

If you use the bulletin board or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. __

###   
**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page, or by emailing our Customer Support at [Contact Us](http://www.gettingmarried.co.uk/contactus.php).

### **  
Security**

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us via [Contact Us](http://www.gettingmarried.co.uk/contactus.php)

###   
Business Transitions

In the event Incubate goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.  You will be notified via email and a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

###   
Changes in this Privacy Statement 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

###   
Contact Us 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us via our contact form at [Contact Us](http://www.gettingmarried.co.uk/contactus.php), or our parent company Incubate at [Incubate](http://www.incubate.co.uk/).
